We are monsters
우린 몬스터
we are proud
우린 자랑스러워
We are monsters
우린 몬스터
say it loud!
크게 외쳐!
High school's a horror
고등학교는 공포지
Can't get out of my bed
내 침대에서 나가고 싶지 않아
Everybody's talking
모두들 얘기하고 있지만
but it's not in my head
내용이 머리에 들어오질 않아
They say,
그들은 말하지,
don’t be different
달라지려 하지 마
be like them instead
그들의 대신처럼 되 버리니까
But they can't keep us a down
하지만 그들은 우리를 계속 진정시킬 수 없어
cause' we're Monster High bred
왜냐면 우리는 몬스터하이에서 자랐으니까
The clock is striking 13
시계가 13시를 가리켜
(Whoa oh oh oh)
It's time to cheer for your team
너희 팀을 응원할 시간이야
(Whoa oh oh oh)
You are ghoulest ghoul
너는 괴물다운 괴물보다
by far
더 멋져
So don’t be afraid of
그러니까 네가 누구인지 생각하며
who you are!!!
두려워 하지 마!!!
Cause' tonight were gonna leave our fears behind
왜냐면 오늘 밤 우리는 우리의 공포 뒤로 떠났어
We're in it together
우리는 함께 있어
Stepping out and
뛰어올라서
we're letting our spirits fly
우리의 영혼을 날게 하는 거야
(Oh yeah!)
Stay fierce forever
영원히 맹렬한 상태야
Wa
wa
wa oh
Freak out if you dare
흥분할테면 해봐
Wa
wa
wa oh
Your best nightmare
넌 최고의 악몽이야
Don’t!
멈추지!
stop
마!
rocking your right to fright
멋지게 너의 공포의 권리를 써
We are Monster High
우린 몬스터하이
We are monsters,
우린 몬스터,
we are proud
우린 자랑스러워
We are monsters,
우린 몬스터,
say it loud
크게 외쳐
We are monsters,
우린 몬스터,
we are proud
우린 자랑스러워
We are monsters,
우린 몬스터,
say it loud!
크게 외쳐!
Perfectly imperfect,
완벽하게 불완전해,
and we do it our way
그리고 우린 우리의 길을 갈 거야
United not divided
단결하면 찢어지지 않고
won't get cast away
혼자 떨어지는 건 원하지 않아
They say,
그들은 말하지,
go run and hide
가서 달리고 숨어라
But I just gotta say
하지만 난 그냥 이렇게 말하지
We're drop dead gorgeous
우리는 전부 매일
each and every day
넋이 나가게 멋지다고
The clock is striking 13
시계가 13시를 가리켜
(Whoa oh oh oh)
It's time to cheer for your team
너희 팀을 응원할 시간이야
(Whoa oh oh oh)
We don't have to say goodbye
우리는 잘가라고 말하지 않아
Cause' friends like these will
왜냐면 친구들은 절대 죽지
never die!!!
않을 거니까!!!
Cause' tonight were gonna leave our fears behind-
왜냐면 오늘 밤 우리는 우리의 공포 뒤로 떠났어-
We're in it together
우리는 함께 있어
Stepping out and
뛰어올라서
we're letting our spirits fly
우리의 영혼을 날게 하는 거야
(Oh yeah!)
Stay fierce forever
영원히 맹렬한 상태야
Wa
wa
wa oh
Freak out if you dare
흥분할테면 해봐
Wa
wa
wa oh
Your best nightmare
넌 최고의 악몽이야
Don’t!
멈추지!
stop
마!
rocking your right to fright
멋지게 너의 공포의 권리를 써
We are Monster High
우린 몬스터하이
We are monsters,
우린 몬스터,
we are proud
우린 자랑스러워
We are monsters,
우린 몬스터,
say it loud
크게 외쳐
We are monsters,
우린 몬스터,
we are proud
우린 자랑스러워
We are monsters,
우린 몬스터,
say it loud!
크게 외쳐!
Cause' tonight were gonna leave our fears behind
왜냐면 오늘 밤 우리는 우리의 공포 뒤로 떠났어
We're in it together
우리는 함께 있어
Come on!
어서!
It's time to let out spirits fly!
네 영혼을 해방시켜 날게 할 시간이야!
Stay fierce forever
영원히 맹렬한 상태야
Wa
wa
wa oh
Freak out if you dare
흥분할테면 해봐
Wa
wa
wa oh
Your best nightmare
넌 최고의 악몽이야
Don’t!
멈추지!
stop!
마!
rocking your right to fright
멋지게 너의 공포의 권리를 써
We are Monster High
우린 몬스터하이
We are monsters, we are proud
우린 몬스터, 우린 자랑스러워
We are monsters, say it loud(We are Monster High)
우린 몬스터, 크게 외쳐(우린 몬스터 하이)
We are monsters, we are proud
우린 몬스터, 우린 자랑스러워
We are monsters
우린 몬스터
We are Monster High
우린 몬스터 하이